Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1949-1992, 119387
  - Bizios, Rena - Bioengineering/Chemical Engineering, 1987-1988; 170005 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Blanco, Herminio - Economics, 1980-1987; 170006 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Blau, Zena Smith - Sociology, 1984; 170007 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Blue, James B. - Fine Arts/Director of Rice Media Center, 1972-1978; 170008 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Borbridge, David C. - Religious Studies, 1972-1983; 170009 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Borchelt, J. Gregg - Architecture, 1983-1985; 170010 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Bortz, Daniel - Shepherd School of Music, 1986; 170011 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Bowie, Norman, E. - Business Ethics, 1986; 170012 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Boyd, Harold B., Jr. - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1986; 170013 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Brabson, John Samuel - Biochemistry, 1978-1984; 170014 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Brady, Patrick - French and Italian, 1972-1988; 170015 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Brakhage, Stan - Mellon Professor of Humanities, 1986; 170016 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Brosch, Gary L. - Administration, 1987-1988; 170017 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Brown, Allyson - Shepherd School of Music, 1982-1984; 170018 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Brown, Arthur Morton - Biology, 1985-1989; 170019 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Brown, Martin Bryson - Philosophy, 1983-1984; 170020 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Browning, Richard E. - Administration, 1987; 170021 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Bryant, Robert L. - Mathematics, 1979-1988; 170022 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Buchholz, Rogene A. - Business Ethics, 1987; 170023 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Byrd, Richard H. - Mathematical Sciences, 1987-1988; 170024 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Canty, Anne P. - Health and Physical Education, 1986-1987; 170025 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Carl, Peter - Architecture, 1985; 170026 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Carp, Robert A. - Political Science, 1986; 170027 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Carpenter, Sandra L. - Psychology, 1984-1986; 170028 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Casey, Richard E. - Geology, 1972-1987; 170029 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Castleman, Heidi - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1984; 170030 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Chadwick, Jonathan - English, 1987; 170031 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Chakrabarty, J. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1983-1984; 170032 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Chang, Sheldon Xu-Dong - Mathematics, 1988-1989; 170033 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Ching, Julia C. - Religious Studies, 1985-1989; 170034 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Chismar, Ronald F. - Assistant Head Coach/Defensive Coordinator, 1987-1988; 170035 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Chow, Bennett - Mathematics, 1987-1988; 170036 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Clark, Howard C., Jr. - Geology and Geophysics, 1966-1992; 170037 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Clarke, Sally - History, 1986-1987; 170038 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Clifford, Dennis A. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1984; 170039 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Collie, Melissa P. - Political Science, 1982-1984; 170040 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Collier, John D. - Philosophy, 1986-1987; 170041 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Comissiona, Sergiu - Shepherd School of Music, 1982-1988; 170042 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Coscio, Elizabeth A. - Spanish, 1986-1987; 170043 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Cosgrove, Michael H. - Administrative Science, 1986; 170044 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Cox, Donald P. - Space Physics and Astronomy/Mathematical Sciences, 1979-1980, 1983-1984; 170045 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Craig, Anna M. - Administrative Science, 1984; 170046 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Cuff, Dana Charlene - Architecture, 1983-1986; 170047 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Cunningham, Kevin F. - Administrative Science, 1981-1987; 170048 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Dahleh, Munther - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1987; 170049 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Davis, Harold L. - Physics, 1985; 170050 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Davis, Kathleen A. - Health and Physical Education, 1984-1988; 170051 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - DeBellas, Alfred F., Jr. - Administration, 1981-1986; 170052 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - de la Reza, Rey - Architecture, 1986; 170053 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Desensi, Joy Theresa - Health and Physical Education, 1980-1984; 170054 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Devlin, Jacqueline J. - Economics, 1984-1985, 1987-1988; 170055 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Dewitt, John Adams - Shpeherd School of Music, 1982-1989; 170056 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Dickey (McFall), June A. - Health and Physical Education, 1974-1984; 170057 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Dillon, Patrick - Architecture, 1985; 170058 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Donegan, Michael K. - Mathematical Sciences/Computer Science, 1981-1984; 170060 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Doshi, Kshitij A. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1987-1988; 170061 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Douglas, Andrew S. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1981-1983; 170062 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Dowden, Wilfred S. - English, 1949-1987; 170063 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Dressel, Linda L. - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1982-1988; 170064 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Duke, Michael B. - Geology, 1979-1985; 170065 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Duke, Reese D. - Education (photograph), 1966-1990; 170066 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Dunn, Josephine Marie - Art and Art History, 1986-1988; 170067 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Dunne, Edward G. - Mathematics, 1984-1987; 170068 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Dunne, Timothy T. - Mathematical Sciences, 1986-1987; 170069 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Dvoretzky, Aaron - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1987; 170070 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Dwyer, Peggy D. - Accounting, 1982-1984; 170071 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Dyer, James C., IV - Economics, 1989; 170072 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Edwards, George - Geology and Geophysics, 1983-1988; 170073 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Elan, Benjamin A. - History, 1985-1986; 170074 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - England, Anthony Wayne - Geology and Geophysics, 1987-1989; 170075 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Epperson, Anne E. - Shepherd School of Music (offer not accepted), 1984; 170076 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Erickson, John D. - French, 1988-1989; 170077 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Estreicher, Steven - Physics/Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1984-1986; 170078 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Evans, Benny Dan - Mathematics, 1980-1981, 1984-1985, 1988; 170079 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Evans, John Wynne - Mathematical Sciences, 1977; 170084 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Evans, Paul - Economics, 1986; 170085 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Evans, Richard I. - Psychology, n.d.; 170086 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Farrell, John P. - English, 1989; 170087 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Farrell, Michele L. - French and Italian, 1988 [?]; 170088 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Feder, Roland - Physics, 1985-1986; 170089 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Feher, Edward P. - Psychology, 1987; 170090 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Fisher, Phil Stuart - Humanities, 1987-1988; 170091 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Fitch, James A. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1987-1988; 170092 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Fitzsimmons, Michael P. - History, 1983-1985; 170093 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Flapan, Erica - Mathematics, 1983-1985; 170094 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Frampton, Kenneth - Architecture, 1985; 170095 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Frey, Sylvia Rae - History, 1984-1985; 170096 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Frol, Alan Belmore - Psychology, 1986; 170097 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Gargi, Satya P. - Geology and Geophysics, 1985-1986; 170098 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Ghazzaly, Osman I. - Civil Engineering, 1972-1988; 170099 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Gibson, James L. - Political Science, 1985; 170100 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Gillman, Susan K. - English, 1982-1986; 170101 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Ginsburg, Barbara - German and Russian, 1981-1984; 170102 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Glazer, Jacob - Economics (offer not accepted), 1986; 170103 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Glitsch, Val - Architecture, 1987; 170104 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Goggin, Malcolm L. - Political Science, 1987; 170105 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Gold, Eva - English, 1984-1985; 170106 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Goldstein, Jane McCarthy - Education, 1984-1985; 170107 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Golson, William G. - Computer Science, 1983-1988; 170108 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Gonzalez, Ruben D. - Shepherd School of Music, 1981-1986; 170109 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Graham, Charles Robin - Mathematics, 1986-1987; 170110 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Graham, Daniel W. - Philosophy, 1984-1986; 170111 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Grayson, Marion - Art and Art History/Director of the Sewall Art Gallery, 1983-1987; 170112 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Greanias, George C. - Administrative Science, 1977-1986; 170113 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Greene, Alison de Lima - Art and Art History, 1989; 170114 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Gregerson, Kenneth James - Linguistics, 1987-1988; 170115 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Gregory, Nathaniel A. - Administrative Science, 1991; 170116 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Grimes, A. Ray - Administrative Science, 1984; 170117 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Hagigi, Moshe - Accounting, 1982-1989; 170118 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Halpin, John F. - Philosophy, 1984-1985; 170119 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Harvey, Robert J. - Psychology, 1982-1987; 170120 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Haske, Carl - Mathematics, 1986-1987; 170121 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Hatfield, Jennifer Margaret - Psychology, 1985; 170122 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Hatton, Gregory - Physics, 1979-1987; 170123 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Heckman, Leila - Administrative Science, 1985-1986; 170124 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Heile, John - Architecture, 1984-1988; 170125 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Hewitt, Mark A. - Architecture, 1982-1985; 170126 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Hill, N. Ross - Geophysics, 1984-1986; 170127 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Hillerbrand, Hans J. - Religious Studies, 1987-1988; 170128 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Hinich, Mel - Autry Chair candidate, 1982; 170129 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Hirs, Edward A., III - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1985; 170130 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Hirschey, Mark - Administrative Science, 1986-1988; 170131 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Hiscoe, Carol B. - English, 1985-1986; 170132 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Hsu, Laura H. L. - Biology, 1980-1984; 170133 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Huber, Stephen K. - Political Science, 1983-1988; 170134 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Ku, Hung-Ting - History, 1986; 170135 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Hunt, Mary - Shepherd School of Music, 1984-1985; 170136 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Irwin, Robert - Architecture, 1987-1988; 170137 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Jackson, John B. - Architecture, 1986; 170138 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Jeys, Thomas H. - Physics, 1982-1985; 170139 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Johannson, Klaus - Mathematics, 1985-1986; 170140 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Johnson, Robert E. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1979-1984; 170141 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Johnson, Sheila - German, 1984-1986; 170142 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Jones, Donald G. - Business Ethics, 1984; 170143 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Jones, Sidney L. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1986; 170144 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kasper, Jerome V. V. - Chemistry, 1982-1989; 170145 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kasschau, Richard A. - Psychology, 1987; 170146 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Kaul, J. Mikael - Architecture, 1987-1988; 170147 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kelly, Kirk Patrick - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1981-1985; 170148 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kim, Dae Mann - Electrical Engineering, 1970-1986; 170149 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kisic, Alemka - Biochemistry, 1977-1978; 170150 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Kluger, Brian - Economics, 1985-1987; 170151 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Kluger, Luisa - Spanish, 1984-1985; 170152 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Kohn, Wolf - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1981-1987; 170153 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Kolla, Venkatarathnam - Geology, 1983-1984; 170154 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Kornbluh, Mark L. - History, 1985-1986; 170155 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Kossowski, Marek - Mathematics, 1983-1986; 170156 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Kostof, Spiro - Architecture, 1986-1987; 170157 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Kraus, Philip C. - Shepherd School of Music, 1981-1985; 170158 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Kretlow, William J. - Economics, 1984-1985; 170159 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Kreuzer, Paul - Health and Physical Education, 1979-1980, 1983, 1986; 170160 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Krieger, Alex - Architecture, 1987; 170161 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Kroopnick, Peter M. - Geology, 1983-1986; 170162 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Kruk, Jeffrey - Physics, 1986-1987; 170163 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Lande, Arnold J. - Electrical Engineering, 1980-1985; 170164 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Landsman, Julie - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1986; 170165 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Lantz, Mary Jean - Education, 1986; 170166 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Leach, William J. - Civil Engineering, 1987; 170167 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Lee, Eun Sul - Psychology, 1982-1985; 170168 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Lemr, John - Architecture, 1986; 170169 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Lester, Richard - Art and Art History, 1985; 170170 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Levine, Richard B. - Biology, 1982-1988; 170171 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Lickman, Stephen S. - Shepherd School of Music, 1982-1985; 170172 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Lipartito, Kenneth J. - History, 1987-1988; 170173 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Litherland, Richard A. - Mathematics, 1985-1986; 170175 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Loutzenheiser, Roy Clyde - Civil Engineering, 1981-1988; 170176 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Lower, Janna - Shepherd School of Music, 1987-1988; 170177 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Lowry, Beverly - English, 1987; 170178 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Lucariello, Georgann - Health and Physical Eduction, 1983-1984; 170179 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Lynn, George - Shepherd School of Music, 1986-1987; 170180 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - McAlister, Alfred L. - Psychology, 1983-1985; 170181 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - McCoin, Ken - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1985; 170182 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - McCormick, Peggy V. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1983-1988; 170183 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - McGee, R. Jon - Anthropology (offer not accepted), 1984-1985; 170184 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - McHugh, Patrick J. - Administrative Science, 1985-1987; 170185 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - McKinley, Frank - Shepherd School of Music, 1987-1988; 170186 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - MacCallum, Iain - Computer Science, 1984; 170187 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Machado, Rodolfo - Architecture, 1986-1987; 170188 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Magrino, Francis J. - Economics, 1984-1988; 170189 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Makavejev, Dusan - Film Studies, 1986; 170190 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Mandel, James Paul - Administrative Science, 1978-1984; 170191 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Mangurian, Robert - Architecture, 1988; 170192 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Manscareck, Clyde L. - Religious Studies, 1983-1987; 170193 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Marzio, Peter C. - History (offer not accepted), 1984-1985; 170194 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Mascarenhas, Briance - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1980-1986; 170195 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Mattern, Ruth - Philosophy, 1981-1984; 170196 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Matty, David J. - Geology, 1983-1985; 170197 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Mauldin, Charles R. - Administrative Science, 1980-1987; 170198 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - May, William W. - Business Ethics, 1985; 170199 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Meeks, William H. - Mathematics, 1984-1986; 170200 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Mellnas, Arne - Shepherd School of Music, 1985; 170201 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Meza, Juan C. - Mathematical Sciences, 1987; 170202 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Miller, Edward M. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1981-1984; 170203 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Molder, Robert P. - Humanities, 1983-1985; 170204 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Morris, Deborah - Architecture, 1987-1988; 170206 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Moss, Eric O. - Architecture, 1988-1989; 170207 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Nakata, Mie - Mathematical Sciences, 1986; 170208 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Navarro, Javier - Architecture, 1987; 170209 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Nitz, David E. - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1985-1986; 170210 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Norholm, Ib - Shepherd School of Music, 1988; 170211 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Norstrom, Carl - Accounting, 1984; 170212 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Ochsner, Jeffrey Karl - Architecture, 1982-1988; 170213 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Oliver, Douglas - Architecture, 1987-1988; 170214 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Oliver-Smith, Philip - Art and Art History, 1969-1988; 170215 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - O'Neil, John - History, 1965-1988; 170216 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Oppenheimer, Bruce I. - Political Science, 1985, 1988; 170217 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Panko, Walter B. - Computer Science, 1985-1988; 170218 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Parfit, Derek - Philosophy, 1984; 170219 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Payton, Neil - Architecture, 1985-1986; 170220 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Pearson, Deborah - Psychology, 1986-1987; 170221 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Phillips, Lyn Bracewell - Humanities, 1986-1989; 170222 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Pithyachariyakul, Pipat - Economics, 1982-1984; 170223 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Pollitt, Ernesto - Anthropology, 1981-1986; 170224 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Ponder, Jay W. - Chemistry, 1984-1985; 170225 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Procunier, James Douglas - Biology, 1979-1985; 170226 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Queller, David Charles - Biology, 1984-1987; 170227 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Rajan, Arvind - Mathematical Sciences, 1985-1986; 170228 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Rakes, (N.F.N) - Mathematical Sciences, 1986; 170229 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Rasmussen, David Tab - Anthropology, 1987-1988; 170230 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Retiz, Leonard - German, 1986-1987; 170231 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Richards, Gwyn - Shepherd School of Music, 1980-1986; 170232 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Robinson, Edward - Geology and Geophysics, 1985-1988; 170233 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Robinson, Joan Seeman - Art and Art History, 1984; 170234 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Roca, Miguel A. - Architecture, 1986; 170235 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rosborough, James W. - Adminstrative Science, 1985-1989; 170236 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Ross, Robert L. - Administrative Science, 1983-1986; 170237 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Ross, Ronald S. - Administrative Science, 1982-1987; 170269 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Rothberg, Robert H. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1988; 170270 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Rowe, Peter G. - Architecture, 1971-1985; 170271 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Rowley, Richard L. - Chemical Engineering, 1978-1983; 170272 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Rudnick, Andrew J. - Administrative Science, 1982-1986; 170273 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Ruekberg, Benjamin P. - Chemistry, 1985-1986; 170274 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Ruffin, Roy J. - Economics, 1988; 170275 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Sachs, Ekkehard Wolfgang - Mathematical Sciences, 1989; 170276 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Sanders, M. Elizabeth - Political Science, 1977-1984; 170277 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Sanders, Susan - Health and Physical Education, 1985-1988; 170278 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Savino, Charles - Architecture, 1982-1984; 170280 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Sawyer, Ronald C. - History, 1985-1986; 170281 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Scheid, Mark - English, 1984; 170282 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Scherfig, Jan - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1985; 170283 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Schey, Richard A. - Administrative Science, 1985; 170284 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Schmitz, William E. - Philosophy, 1984-1986; 170285 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Schneider, Carole M. - Health and Physical Education, 1986-1987; 170286 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Schreiber, B. Charlotte - Geology, 1982-1986; 170287 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Schotten, Yizhak - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1985; 170288 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Schwartz, Lynne S. - English, 1987; 170289 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Schwarzer, Rudy R. - Geology and Geophysics, 1974-1989; 170290 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Scogin, Mack - Architecture, 1986; 170291 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Scott, Julius S., III - History, 1986-1987; 170292 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Segner, Edmund P., III - Civil Engineering, 1982-1984; 170293 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Sepos, Charles - Shepherd School of Music, 1986-1987; 170294 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Shackelford, George T. M. - Art and Art History, 1988; 170296 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Shalen, Peter B. - Mathematics, 1974-1986; 170297 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Shange, Ntozake - English, 1982-1983; 170298 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Shapiro, Danny - Philosophy, 1984-1986; 170299 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Shaw, Bill - Business Ethics, 1987; 170300 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Shaw, John P. - Architecture, 1988; 170301 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Shaw, Stephanie - History, 1987-1988; 170302 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Shields, P. David - Accounting, 1983-1988; 170303 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Shmider, Edward - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1986; 170304 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Singer, Steven J. - Accounting, 1983-1987; 170305 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Sistare, Christine T. - Philosophy, 1983-1986; 170306 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Sloan, John W. - Political Science, 1987; 170307 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Slutsky, Steven M. - Economics, 1986; 170308 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Smith, Allan Otho - Art and Art History, 1988; 170309 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Smith, Eugene L. - Political Science, 1983-1986; 170310 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Smith, Penny - Mathematics, 1985-1986; 170311 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Smith, Vinson C. - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1986; 170312 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Sorensen, Henrik - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1986-1987; 170313 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Sorenson, Kenneth G. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1987; 170314 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Spivak, Michael D. - Mathematics, 1984-1986; 170315 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Spurr, Michael J. - Mathematics, 1984-1987; 170316 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Stainbrook, Gene - Psychology, 1985-1986; 170317 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Stallones, Reuel A. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1977-1986; 170318 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Stanbury, David M. - Chemistry, 1980-1987; 170319 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Stanton, R. John, Jr. - Administrative Science, 1983-1989; 170320 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Steffey, Marda N. - Jones Graduate School of Administration, 1984-1987; 170321 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Steiner, Erich - Linguistics, 1986; 170322 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Stevenson, Brenda E. - Humanities, 1986-1987; 170323 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Stingl, Michael J. - Philosophy, 1986-1988; 170324 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Stoller, Jennie - English, 1986-1987; 170325 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Stott, Richard B. - History, 1986-1987; 170326 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Swan, Llewellyn Alex - Sociology, 1988; 170327 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Terrell, George R. - Mathematical Sciences, 1980-1986; 170328 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Terry, Carolyn Ann - Education, 1987; 170329 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Thomas, Jay C. - Psychology, 1981-1984; 170330 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Thomson, William C., Jr. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1987-1988; 170331 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Tibbits, Patrick A. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1988; 170332 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Tipton, Albert N. - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-1988; 170333 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Tipton (Norris), Mary A. - Shepherd School of Music, 1975-1988; 170334 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Todorov, Andrey - Mathematics, 1987; 170335 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Tucker, Kenneth H., Jr. - Sociology, 1985-1988; 170336 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Turbeville, Fred Morton - Naval Science, [?]-1969; 170337 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Turner, Drexel - Architecture, 1974-1985; 170338 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Underhill, Michael - Architecture, 1979-1988; 170339 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Valkovic, Vlado - Physics, 1970-1988; 170340 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Valley, John W. - Geology, 1980-1985; 170341 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Vandergriff, Kim D. - Biochemistry, 1984-1985; 170342 (Box 19, Folder 3)